

Drongensesteenweg 241 Bus 207 9000, Ghent

C

+32 473 67 79 76

 \square

florian.landuyt@hotmail.com



10/05/1996, Ghent



unmarried



A3, B

Language skills

Dutch – native language English – very good French – moderate

Soft skills

Discipline
Engagement
Inquisitiveness
Teamplayer
Stress resistance

Hobbies

Gymnastics Ski Travel Karting

Florian Landuyt

Bachelor of Applied Informatics

I am 24 years old, born in Belgium, eager to learn and very interested in the most recent and innovative technology.

Putting the team spirit above individual success is something I always aim for.

I am always searching for opportunities and new ways to broaden and improve my soft – and hard skills.

Education

2016 – 2021 HoGent

Bachelor Applied Informatics Specialization Mobile Apps

2008 – 2014 KA Voskenslaan

General secondary education Sciences - Topsport

Relevant work experiences

2007 - Now Sport Vlaanderen

Elite sport – National team Artistic Gymnastics Top 24 All-round – WC Glasgow 2015

2016 – 2019 Uitzenda:

Student job catering

Uitzendgastronomie

Hard skills

HTML & CSS

C# .Net framework

Kotlin

Angular

Java

Typescript

Swift

SQL

ML in Python

Interests

Artificial intelligence Machine learning UI & UX

Projects and references

Available on request